The feed mill is finally on track
Using my forest frogs as live advertisements
Demand outstripped supply as soon as they launched
While buying the feed mill
The forest frog farm also expanded
I leased a mountain in the village
Released the forest frogs from the greenhouses
Letting them grow naturally in the mountains
Oh my Daniel
You've suffered so much
You've lost weight
It's all that damned Lewes's fault
Lewes, Cynthia
I will have my revenge
Daniel
I've been waiting so long for you
You're finally out
Brian, what do you want
The money I owe you
Zoe already paid it back
She committed tax evasion
Her accounts were wiped clean
That money was seized by the Tax Bureau
So you still have to pay back